A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Correspondence Files FA1283
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Friends and Associates, 1962-1991; 2; 11.4 Cubic Feet 26 document boxes, 1 oversized flat box.
  The Friends and Associates series contains named files pertaining to individual friends, relatives, and business associates, spanning the period 1962-1991. Some of the files are true correspondence files, whereas others may cover only a few years' period or may complement additional correspondence in the Alphabetical series. In many cases, the files pertain to memorial arrangements and tributes. Files may also pertain to particular projects undertaken with support from LSR or on his behalf.
  The series also includes files for individual Consultants, Employees, and Personnel. Most notably, an extensive series of "Personnel" files for LSR's associate Clayton W. (Wes) Frye helps document his working relationship with LSR, various projects he followed, and his professional and board memberships, from 1973 to the late 1980s.
  The files found in the Friends and Associates series come from LSR's papers in the Rockefeller Family general files, record groups 3, 33, 37, and 39.
  The Friends and Associates files are arranged in a single alphabetical series by name, followed by categorized files for individual Consultants, Employees, and Personnel.
  - Albright, Horace M., 1962-1965 (Box 27, Folder 178)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 179)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 180)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1977-1981 (Box 27, Folder 181)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 182)
    Includes two snapshots of Albright, including one on his 94th birthday (1984).
  - Albright, Horace M., 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 183)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 184)
  - Albright, Horace M., 1988 September (Box 27, Folder 185)
    File contains Joseph Ernst's outline, summaries, and calendar of correspondence for his proposed edition of the correspondence of JDR Jr. and Horace Albright (Worthwhile Places).
  - Albright, Horace M., 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 186)
  - Barton, Robert S., 1981 January - April (Box 28, Folder 187)
  - Barton, Robert S. and Sheila Barton, 1981 May - 1986 (Box 28, Folder 188)
  - Barton, Robert S. (Condolences and Acknowledgments), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 189)
  - Barton, Robert S. ( Memorial Booklet and Mailing Lists), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 190)
  - Barton, Robert S. (Obituaries), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 191)
  - Boltin, Lee, 1989 -1993 (Box 28, Folder 192 -193)
    Correspondence concerning television program on "Images of Jesus."
  - Firestone, Leonard K., 1982-1986 (Box 28, Folder 194)
  - French, John, Jr. and Eleanor Clark French, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 195)
  - French, John, Jr., 1984 August - September (Box 28, Folder 196)
    Obituaries and funeral services.
  - French, Eleanor Clark, 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - French, John III and Marina Kellen Gundlach, 1981-1991 (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - French, Lawrence C., 1982-1991 (Box 29, Folder 199)
  - Galbraith, Marie (Mrs. Evan G., Jr.), 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 200)
    Separated Materials
    Includes photos of Marion R. Weber and Brendan O'Regan, 1990.
  - Guion, Connie, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 201)
  - Gustafson, Carl O., 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 202)
  - Gustafson, Carl O., Jr.: General, 1963-1970, 1987-1990 (Box 29, Folder 203)
  - Gustafson, Carl O., Jr.: Shelter Island Property, 1987-1990, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 204 - 207)
  - Hanks, Nancy: Correspondence, 1961, 1963-1976 (Box 30, Folder 208)
  - Hanks, Nancy: General, 1977-1982 (Box 30, Folder 209)
    Includes two black and white portraits of Nancy Hanks, and copy of photo of LSR and Nelson Rockefeller on horseback on Adirondack trip, October 10-11, 1965.
  - Hanks, Nancy: General, 1983-1988 (Box 30, Folder 210)
    Includes correspondence, 1986-1988, concerning a biography project, and a snapshot of Nancy and Virginia Hanks.
  - Hanks, Nancy: General (A - O), 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 211 - 212)
    Correspondence concerning memorials, tributes, and estate matters.
  - Hanks, Nancy: General (Partners for Livable Places), 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 213)
    Tribute to Nancy Hanks program, December 1982.
  - Hanks, Nancy: General (Property - Z), 1982-1985 (Box 30, Folder 214)
  - Hanks, Nancy: General (Property - Z), 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 214A)
    Restricted. Material in Rockefeller Family collections pertaining to living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
  - Hanks, Nancy: Duke University, Nancy Hanks Endowment Fund, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 215)
  - Hanks, Nancy: Duke University, Nancy Hanks Endowment Fund, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 215A)
  - Hanks, Nancy - Estate, 1983-1987 (Box 31, Folder 216 - 219)
  - Hanks, Nancy - Memorial Service, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 220 - 225)
    Includes service arrangements, booklets, eulogy, pallbearers, and thank you letters. Some files maintained by Celeste Sismilich. Memorial service held January 18, 1983. Includes black and white photos and contact sheets of the service and the recessional (with LSR) (folders 220-221).
  - Hanks, Nancy - Nancy Hanks Center (Old Post Office), 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 226 - 228)
  - Hanks, Nancy - Obituaries and Printed Material, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 229 - 230)
  - Hanks, Nancy - Tributes, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 231 - 233)
    General tributes and memorial resolutions.
  - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French - Memorial Service, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 234 - 236)
    Includes obituary, service booklet, and acknowledgment lists.
  - Hitchcock, Ethan Allen and Elizabeth French, 1966-1976 (Box 33, Folder 237)
  - Hitchcock Ethan Allen, 1977-1991 (Box 33, Folder 238 - 240)
  - Hughes, Emmet J., 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 241)
    Hughes served as a Rockefeller advisor. File includes Hughes to Nelson A. Rockefeller, July 31, 1962, on political situation in Europe; and proposals to Teddy Walkowicz concerning rooftop playgrounds for New York City.
  - Johnson, Georgia M., 1986-1991 (Box 33, Folder 242)
  - Johnson, Georgia M., 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 242A)
    Restricted - Confidential material. Open in 2029.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird and Lyndon Baines Johnson, 1964-1971 (Box 33, Folder 243 - 245)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1972-1983 (Box 33, Folder 246 - 247)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1984-1991 (Box 34, Folder 248 - 249)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird and Lyndon Baines Johnson (Clippings), 1966-1976 (Box 34, Folder 250)
  - Johnson, Lady Bird and Lyndon Baines Johnson (Dinner Honoring), 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 251)
    Dinner and dance at the Plaza Hotel, January 13, 1969.
  - Johnson, Lady Bird and Lyndon Baines Johnson (LBJ Ranch Visit)), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 252)
    File also includes Lady Bird Johnson's address National Council of State Garden Clubs and American Forestry Association, Jackson Hole, September 7, 1965.
  - Lanier, Jean and Sidney (General), 1986-1991 (Box 34, Folder 253)
    Correspondence; LSR itineraries and meetings with Laniers at Institute of Noetic Sciences; projects and activities.
  - Lanier, Jean and Sidney (Apartment Transactions), 1987-1988 (Box 34, Folder 254 - 256)
  - Lanier, Jean and Sidney (Financial Arrangements), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 257 - 258)
  - Lanier, Jean and Sidney Lanier (Financial Arrangements), 1987 September - 1991 (Box 35, Folder 259 - 261)
  - Matousek, Jiri, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 262)
  - Matousek, Otakar, 1952, 1957-1985 (Box 35, Folder 263 - 269)
    LSR first met Matousek on his Princeton geology trip in 1930. Files include correspondence with Matousek and family. LSR helped fund visiting professorships for Matousek at Cornell and Berkeley in 1965 and 1971-1972. Includes some description of the 1968 Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia. Includes 4 photos of Otakar and Bozena Matousek, Milos Matousek, and students, 1975-1982 (in folders 266-268).
  - Matousek, Otakar and Bozena (Publications and Printed Material), 1959-1971 (Box 35, Folder 270)
    Includes: "Darwinism in Bohemia," 1959; article in Czech on J. E. Purkinje, 1961; "Purkinje's contributions and views before and after the foundation of the cellular theory," 1971.
  - Maze, Etienne, 1980-1986 (Box 36, Folder 271 - 273)
    Includes photographs of Etienne and Margaret Maze and grape harvest, 1980, 1985; LSR and MFR visit, 1981; photos of Achnacloic, Scotland, and Mill at St. George's Motel.
  - Maze, Paul, 1952 - 1978 (Box 36, Folder 274 - 281)
    Photos of Jessie Maze and dogs, artwork, interior and exterior shots of Paul Maze house, garden, and views, Maze with Randolph Churchill, 1953-1966, 1972-1978. File includes undated pencil sketch of man sitting behind desk at "Room 1500" (in folder 279)
  - Maze, Paul, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 281A)
  - Maze, Paul, and Jessie Maze, 1979-1982 (Box 36, Folder 282 - 283)
    Includes two undated photos of Maze sketching and of Jessie Maze with dog.
  - Maze, Paul, 1983-1985 (Box 37, Folder 284-285)
    Memorial book project on Paul Maze (Anne Singer, The Lost Impressionist). File includes black and white contact print and negative of Maze pastel, "Soldiers on Parade."
  - Maze, Paul (Book Distribution and Appreciation Letters), 1983-1984 (Box 37, Folder 286)
    Distribution of Anne Singer, Paul Maze: The Lost Impressionist.
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1964-1974 (Box 37, Folder 287 - 288)
    Original letters interfiled with numbered transcripts. Includes pen and ink drawing of "Sea Star," 1970; photos of Paul and Jessie Maze, gardens, dogs, painting, 1971-1974.
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1972-1974 (Box 37, Folder 288A)
    Restricted. Material in the Rockefeller Family collections pertaining to living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 289)
    Original letters interfiled with numbered transcripts.
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1975-1977 (Box 37, Folder 289A)
    Restricted. Material in the Rockefeller Family collection pertaining to living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1978-1983 (Box 37, Folder 290)
  - Maze, Paul (Letters to Mary French Rockefeller and LSR), 1978-1983 (Box 37, Folder 290A)
  - Milton, David M., 1976, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 291)
    LSR Interview by Edith LaGuardia-Hansen, for book about David Milton. File consists of transcripts and drafts of transcripts. Cassette tape of interview separated from file.
    - Laurance S. Rockefeller Interview by Edith LaGuardia Hansen, concerning David Milton, 1991 January 17; 1/4 inch audio cassette; Sound, 33 minutes (AV 15667)
      Access copy available.
      Laurance S. Rockefeller shares his impressions and memories of David Milton, first husband of Abby "Babs" Rockefeller Mauzé.
  - Moore, Leslie H., 1982-1986 (Box 37, Folder 292)
  - Newhall, Charles Watson, Jr., 1945-1971 (Box 37, Folder 293)
    Memo, ca. 1965, on Mauna Kea hotel and golf operations. Newhall worked as aviation advisor to LSR,1946-1947 (Airport Authority; Vitarama and Cinerama); director of Reaction Motors; president, Flight Refueling.
  - Roberts, Ann Rockefeller, 1988-1991 (Box 38, Folder 294)
  - Roberts, Ann Rockefeller, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 295)
    File contains a copy of Roberts' masters thesis, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Road Builder, Landscape Artist: An Intimate Look at his Role in the Development of the Carriage Roads at Acadia National Park.
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - General, 1965-1981 (Box 38, Folder 296)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Campaigns, 1958-1968 (Box 38, Folder 297 - 301)
    Fundraising requests and clippings.
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1956-1974 (Box 38, Folder 302 - 303)
  - Rodriguez, Chi Chi, 1976-1986 (Box 39, Folder 304 - 305)
  - Rodriguez, Chi Chi (Clippings), 1973-1986 (Box 39, Folder 306)
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1979-1986 (Box 39, Folder 307 - 309)
    Files consist of clippings and some correspondence, mainly concerning MSKCC fundraisers. Includes photos of LSR, Happy Rockefeller, MFR, Edward J. Beattie, and Sinatra, at MSKCC benefit events, 1979-1980.
  - Soldwedel, Florence (Mrs. Frederic), 1975-1991 (Box 39, Folder 310 - 312)
    Proposed sale of paintings to government of the Bahamas; 1991 donation of Soldwedel paintings to Bethune-Cooke College.
  - Van der Kemp, Florence and Gerald, 1982-1991 (Box 39, Folder 313 - 315)
    Giverny restoration; Mexican home and travels. Includes snapshots of construction projects (barns and other buildings) and coffee shop at Giverny.
  - Wallace, Dewitt and Lila Acheson, 1981-1986, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 316-317)
  - Webster-Doyle, Terrence and Jean, 1987-1991 (Box 40, Folder 318)
  - Consultants - General (A - Z), 1986-1990 (Box 40, Folder 319)
    Castro, Nash; Lanier, Jean and Sidney; McCormick, Elizabeth; Weissman, Dorothea.
  - Consultants - Andrews, Valerie, 1986-1991 (Box 40, Folder 320)
  - Consultants - Diamond, Henry L., 1981-1991 (Box 40, Folder 321 - 322)
    Includes regular reviews of pending items.
  - Consultants - Swimme, Brian, 1987-1990 (Box 40, Folder 323)
  - Employees - General (A - Z), 1963-1991 (Box 40, Folder 324 - 326)
    Includes Lowell, Hugh; McKenzie, William and Jeannette; MacLoughlin, Bill; Miller, Paul; Neal, William; Nelson, Gunnar; Piorkowski, Eugenia and Jerzy; Ryan, Dennis J.; Sawyer, James; Schretter, Alfred E.; Sterns, Marion; Taxter, Thomas; Varas, Carolos G.; Wheeler, Donald; Woodstock employees.
  - Employees - Bergstrom, Carl, 1972, 1980-1991 (Box 40, Folder 327)
    Woodstock employee.
  - Employees - Browand, Charles, 1959-1960, 1980-1988 (Box 41, Folder 328)
    Chauffeur and bodyguard.
  - Employees - Browand, Charles and Eleanora, 1988-1990 (Box 41, Folder 329)
  - Employees - Byrnes, Dennis, 1988-1991 (Box 41, Folder 330)
    Restricted - Personnel File.
  - Employees - Jones, J. A. Mancey, 1959 (Box 41, Folder 331)
  - Personnel - General (A - Z), 1961-1989 (Box 41, Folder 332 - 334)
    Includes among others: Chorley, Kenneth; Clifton, Elizabeth; Diamond, Henry; Elliot, Victoria; Flores, Joseph; Hanks, Nancy; Hitesman, Walter; Jennen, Joseph; Leddy, Ellen; Ludt, R. E.; McCracken, Jeanne; McFarlane, Euan; Mauro, Linda; Papas, Nicole; Rand, Harry; Hoffman, Anna Rosenberg and Associates; Smith, M. Frederick; Smith, Janet; Whyte, William H.; Windisch, Marie-Louise; Wirth, Conrad; Woodward, Harper.
  - Personnel - Boyer, Allston, 1967-1972 (Box 41, Folder 335 - 336)
    File mainly consists of expense report submissions.
  - Personnel - Boyer, Allston (Condolences), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 337 - 338)
  - Personnel - Boyer, Allston (Obituaries and Tributes), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 339)
    Includes phto of Boyer at Greenacre Park, 1972.
  - Personnel - Boyer, Allston and Louise Boyer, 1973-1975 (Box 41, Folder 340)
  - Personnel - Enos, Elizabeth (Consultant), 1985-1986 (Box 41, Folder 341)
    Work on arranging and cataloging LSR's photograph albums (transferred from 834 Fifth Ave apartment to Rm 5600); film and video transfers.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General, 1973-1974, 1982-1990 (Box 42, Folder 342)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (A) (Box 42, Folder 343 - 345)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (A), 1984-1985 (Box 42, Folder 345A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (B) (Box 42, Folder 346)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (B), 1981, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 346A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (C) (Box 42, Folder 347)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (D) (Box 42, Folder 348)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (E) (Box 42, Folder 349)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (E), 1984-1986 (Box 42, Folder 349A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (F - G) (Box 43, Folder 350)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (H) (Box 43, Folder 351)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (I) (Box 43, Folder 352)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (J) (Box 43, Folder 353)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (K) (Box 43, Folder 354)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (L) (Box 43, Folder 355)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (M) (Box 43, Folder 356)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (M), 1988 (Box 43, Folder 356A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (N - O) (Box 43, Folder 357)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (N - O), 1981-1988 (Box 43, Folder 357A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (P) (Box 44, Folder 358)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (P), 1985 (Box 44, Folder 358A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W. - General (Q - R) (Box 44, Folder 359)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W. - General (Q - R), 1978-1985 (Box 44, Folder 359A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (S - Sporn) (Box 44, Folder 360)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (S - Sporn), 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 360A)
    Restricted. Material in the Rockefeller Family collections pertaining to living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted. Restricted - Confidential financial records.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (Stack - Sutro) (Box 44, Folder 361)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (T) (Box 44, Folder 362)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (U) (Box 44, Folder 363)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (V - Waggoner) (Box 44, Folder 364)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (Walnut - Wyoming) (Box 45, Folder 365 - 366)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - General (X - Z) (Box 45, Folder 367)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Arvida Corporation, 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 368)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Arvida Corporation (Printed Material), 1979, undated (Box 45, Folder 369)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Aspen Group, 1979-1981 (Box 45, Folder 370 - 372)
    Meetings of Real Estate Group.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Aspen Group, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 373)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Auburn Energy Corporation, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 374)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Economic Data, 1974-1976 (Box 46, Folder 375)
    Projections and reports on the economy, especially by Peter L. Bernstein, Inc. Includes published reports.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Energy, 1973-1975 (Box 46, Folder 376)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Memos and Reports), 1973-1979, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 377 - 378)
    Reports from Wes Frye to LSR concerning Hawaiian interests.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Correspondence, A-Z), 1977-1980 (Box 46, Folder 379)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Printed Material - General), 1977-1985 (Box 46, Folder 380 - 381)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Printed Material - Annual Reports), 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 382)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Printed Material - Hawaii Resort Developers Conference), 1977 (Box 46, Folder 383)
    Materials from workshop on "Economics of Resort Development," November 30, 1977.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Printed Material - Maps and Brochures), 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 384)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Hawaii (Printed Material - Oahu Development Conference), 1968-1974 (Box 47, Folder 385 - 387)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1973-1981 (Box 47, Folder 388 - 391)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1979-1981 (Box 47, Folder 391A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 392)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 392A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1984-1986 (Box 47, Folder 393)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Memoranda, 1984-1986 (Box 47, Folder 393A)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - 1901 Van Ness Partners, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 394)
    Condominium project at 1901 Van Ness Avenue, San Francisco, CA.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - 1901 Van Ness Partners, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 395)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Pinehurst Hotel and Country Club, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 396 - 397)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Printed Material, 1973-1986 (Box 48, Folder 398 - 399)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Real Estate Brochures, 1982-1986 (Box 48, Folder 400 - 401)
    Desert Highlands, Scottsdale, AZ; Morningside, Rancho Mirage, CA.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Resumes, A - Z, 1981-1987 (Box 48, Folder 402 - 403)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1975-1980 (Box 49, Folder 404)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 405 - 406)
    Rancho El Tejon Draft Environmental Impact Report. 1981 February 9.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1982 - 1984 June (Box 49, Folder 407 - 410)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1984 July 13 (Box 49, Folder 411 - 412)
    Land Planning Review, Tejon Ranch Company Board Meeting.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1984 July 16 - October (Box 50, Folder 413)
    Includes 1984 Report of Water Conditions and Outlook.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1984 November - 1985 February (Box 50, Folder 414)
    Includes Five-Year Forecast, 1985-1989.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1985 March 15 (Box 50, Folder 415)
    I-5 Corridor Master Plan Design Guidelines.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch, 1985 March - October (Box 50, Folder 416 - 417)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1985 November (Box 50, Folder 418)
    Commercial and Land Use, I-5 Corridor Review.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1985 November - December (Box 50, Folder 419)
    Includes 1986 Budget.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1986 January (Box 50, Folder 420)
    Includes Tejon Corridor Design Guidelines.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1986 February - June (Box 50, Folder 421)
    Includes Preliminary Geologic and Seismic Investigation, Proposed Hazardous Waste Disposal Site, Oso Canyon Area, Tejon Ranch, June 1986.
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Tejon Ranch Company, 1986 July - December (Box 51, Folder 422 - 423)
    Includes booklet for Board of Directors' Meeting, July 15, 1986 (in folder 422).
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Urban Land Institute, 1977-1985 (Box 51, Folder 424 - 428)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Urban Land Institute (Printed Material), 1977-1979 (Box 51, Folder 429 - 430)
  - Personnel - Frye, Clayton W., Jr. - Urban Land Institute (Printed Material), 1980-1981, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 431 - 432)
  - Personnel - Hartzog, George B., Jr., 1972-1982 (Box 52, Folder 433 - 435)
    Includes report, 1972 or later, on techniques of environmental protection of federal park and cultural values, along with extracts from Virgin Islands zoning statutes. Hartzog studying park proposals for St. Croix and St. John; report on valuation of lands to be sold to Grand Teton National Park, 1978; Harper's Ferry, VA property.
  - Personnel - Hartzog, George B., Jr. (Conflict Investigations), 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 436)
    Hartzog consulting and lobbying on park issues; possible conflict of interest - charges dismissed, 1976
  - Personnel - Hotchkiss, Joseph, 1984-1985 (Box 52, Folder 437)
    Hotchkiss was engaged as a consultant to help with LSR's biography project. File includes a photo (cut-out from a larger print) of Sims McGrath, circa 1955.
  - Personnel - Lamb, George R., 1976-1991 (Box 52, Folder 438)
    Includes draft speech on occasion of Lamb's 25th anniversary with office, 1990.